Guide to the Andrew Smith Gallery Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2014 Acquisition
  - Printed material, Series V
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1976-1977 (Box 344)
      Includes Eliot Porter Trees, Ansel Adams, Yosuf Karsh, Annie Leibovitz, Keith Haring, Skeet McAuley, Baron Wolman, Jerry Uelsmann & Maggie Taylor, Ralph Steiner, Willard Van Dyke, Flor Garduno, and Laura Gilpin.
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-1988 (Box 345)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 346)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-1988 (Box 347)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-1988 (Box 348)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, circa 1970s (Box 349)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-1999 (Box 350)
      Includes Walker Evans, Manual Carillo, Adam Clark Vroman, Manfred Heiting, William Giles, Flor Garduno, and William Clift.
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-2010 (Box 351)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-1999 (Box 352)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1902-1976 (Box 353)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1951 (Box 354)
      Includes Edward Curtis, Hurell II, and W. Euguene Smith.
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1980-2010 (Box 355)
      Includes Ruth Bernhard, Andrew Kertesz, Dennis Stock, James Dean, and Brett Weston.
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1980-2010 (Box 356)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1970-2010 (Box 357)
    - Portfolio cases and colophons, 1980-2010 (Box 358)
    - New Mexico imprints, 1950-2010 (Box 359)
    - Catalogs
      - 1973-2010, Dealer catalogs (Box 360)
      - 1973-2010, Dealer catalogs (Box 361)
      - 1980-1999, Dealer catalogs (Box 362)
      - 1980-1999, Dealer catalogs (Box 363)
      - 1980-1999, Dealer catalogs (Box 364)
      - 1970-2010, Dealer catalogs (Box 365)
      - 1970-2010, Dealer catalogs (Box 366)
      - 1963-2004, Museum and non-profit catalogs (Box 367)
      - 1963-2004, Museum and non-profit catalogs (Box 368)
      - 1960-2013, Catalogs (Box 369)
      - 1960-2010, Catalogs (Box 370)
      - 1980-1999, Southeby's catalogs (Box 371)
      - 1993-2000, Southeby's catalogs (Box 372)
      - 2002-2006, Southeby's catalogs (Box 373)
      - 2002-2006, Southeby's catalogs (Box 374)
      - 2007-2012, Southeby's catalogs (Box 375)
      - 1996-2012, Swann (Box 376)
      - 1996-2012, Swann (Box 377)
      - 1989-1999, Swann (Box 378)
      - 2002-2008, Phillip's (Box 379)
      - 2002-2008, Phillip's (Box 380)
      - 1980s-1999, Phillip's (Box 381)
      - 1987-1994, Christie's (Box 382)
      - 1992-1998, Christie's (Box 383)
      - 1999-2002, Christie's (Box 384)
      - 2003-2007, Christie's (Box 385)
      - 2003-2007, Christie's (Box 386)
      - 2008-2012, Christie's (Box 387)
      - 2008-2012, Christie's (Box 388)
      - 1988-2011, Butterfields and Bonham's (Box 389)
      - 2011-2012, Butterfields and Bonham's (Box 390)
      - 2004-2012, Bassenge Grisbach (Box 391)
      - 2004-2012, Bassenge Grisbach (Box 392)
      - 2004-2012, Cowan's (Box 393)
      - 2004-2012, Cowan's (Box 394)
      - 2004-2012, Catalogs (Box 395)
      - 2007-2009, Catalogs (Box 396)
      - 2004-2012, Catalogs (Box 397)
      - 2006-2012, Catalogs (Box 398)
      - 1980-2000, Catalogs (Box 399)
      - 1990-1999, Catalogs (Box 400)
      - 1990-1999, Catalogs (Box 401)
      - 1989-1992, Art Basel (Box 402)
      - 1970-2000, Catalogs (Box 403)
      - 1970-2000, Catalogs (Box 404)
      - 1990-1999, Catalogs (Box 405)
      - 1990-1999, Catalogs (Box 406)
      - 1980-2012, Charles Wood; Behold (Box 407)
      - 2005, Catalogs (Box 408)
      - 2005, Catalogs (Box 409)
      - 2005, Catalogs (Box 410)
      - 1990-2010, Catalogs (Box 411)
      - 2006-2007, Catalogs (Box 412)
      - 1994, Auction catalog (Box 413)
      - 1997-2007, Catalogs (Box 414)
      - 1997-2007, Catalogs (Box 415)
      - 1978-2001, Catalogs (Box 416)
      - 1978-2001, Catalogs (Box 417)
    - Gallery ephemera and other printed material
      - circa 1990-2012, Miscellaneous ephemera and printed (Box 418)
      - 1986-1996, Announcement cards (Box 419)
      - 1982-1998, Announcement cards (Box 420)
      - 1982-1998, Announcement cards (Box 421)
      - 1997, Announcement cards (Box 422)
      - 1997, Announcement cards (Box 423)
      - 1996-1999, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 424)
      - 1996-1999, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 425)
      - 1998-1999, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 426)
      - 1998-1999, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 427)
      - undated, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 428)
      - undated, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 429)
      - 1997-1998, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 430)
      - 1997-1998, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 431)
      - 2001, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 432)
      - 1997-1998, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 433)
      - 1995-1997, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 434)
      - 1997-1998, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 435)
      - circa 1997, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 436)
      - 1997, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 437)
      - 1997, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 438)
      - 1988, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 439)
      - 1988, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 440)
      - 1987-1993, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 441)
      - 2004, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 442)
      - 2004, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 443)
      - 2004, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 444)
      - 2001, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 445)
      - 2001, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 446)
      - 2001, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 447)
      - 1983-1989, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 448)
      - 1986, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 449)
      - 2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 450)
      - 2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 451)
      - 2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 452)
      - 2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 453)
      - 2009, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 454)
      - 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 455)
      - 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 456)
      - 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 457)
      - 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 458)
      - 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 459)
      - 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 460)
      - 1993-2009, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 461)
      - 2008-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 462)
      - 2008-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 463)
      - 2005, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 464)
      - 2005, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 465)
      - 2005, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 466)
      - 2005-2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 467)
      - 2005-2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 468)
      - 2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 469)
      - 2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 470)
      - 2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 471)
      - 2001-2006, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 472)
      - 2001-2006, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 473)
      - 2001-2006, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 474)
      - 2002-2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 475)
      - 2002-2006, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 476)
      - 2005-2006, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 477)
      - 2005-2006, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 478)
      - 2005-2006, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 479)
      - 2012, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 480)
      - circa 2012, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 481)
      - 2012, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 482)
      - 2000-2010, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 483)
      - 2002-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 484)
      - 2002-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 485)
      - 1997-2009, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 486)
      - 2003, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 487)
      - 2010, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 488)
      - 2010, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 489)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 490)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 491)
      - 2004, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 492)
      - 2007-2009, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 493)
      - 2007-2009, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 494)
      - 2007-2008, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 495)
      - 2007-2008, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 496)
      - 1991-2000, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 497)
      - 1991-2000, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 498)
      - 1991-2000, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 499)
      - 1993, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 500)
      - 1991-1992, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 501)
      - 1993, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 502)
      - 2013, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 503)
        May include auction catalogs.
      - 2013, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 504)
      - 2013, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 505)
      - 2013, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 506)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 507)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 508)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 509)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 510)
      - 2007, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 511)
      - 2011, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 512)
      - 2011, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 513)
      - circa 2011, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 514)
      - circa 20011, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 515)
      - 2008-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 516)
      - 2008-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 517)
      - 2008-2009, Gallery ephemera mostly from the American Southwest. (Box 518)
      - 2008-2009, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 519)
      - 1986-1994, Window displays (Box 520)
      - 1986-1994, Window displays (Box 521)
      - 2009-2010, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 522)
      - 1980-1989, Sheila Metzner posters (Box 523)
      - 1980-1989, Sheila Metzner posters (Box 524)
      - 1980-1989, Sheila Metzner posters (Box 525)
      - 1980-1989, Sheila Metzner posters (Box 526)
      - 2013, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 527)
      - 2013, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 528)
      - 2013, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 529)
      - 2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 530)
      - 2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 531)
      - 2013-2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 532)
      - 2013-2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 533)
      - 2013-2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 534)
      - 2013-2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 535)
      - 2013-2014, Miscellaneous mail ephemera (Box 536)
      - undated, Empty photograph albums (Box 537)
      - 1907-1990, Empty photograph albums (Box 538)
      - circa 1970s, Posters (Box 539)
  - Photographic reproductions and related papers, Series VI
    - A - B, 1860-2000 (Box 540)
    - A - B, 1860-2000 (Box 541)
    - A - B, 1860-2000 (Box 542)
    - A - B, 1860-2000 (Box 543)
    - B - C, 1860-2000 (Box 544)
      Includes Rolf Koppell.
    - B - C, 1860-2000 (Box 545)
    - C - E, 1860-2000 (Box 546)
    - C - E, 1860-2000 (Box 547)
    - C - E, 1860-2000 (Box 548)
    - Curtis North American Indians, 1860-2000 (Box 549)
    - Curtis North American Indians, 1860-2000 (Box 550)
    - Curtis North American Indians, 1860-2000 (Box 551)
    - Curtis North American Indians, 1860-2000 (Box 552)
    - F - G, 1860-2000 (Box 553)
      Includes Robert Frank.
    - F - G, 1860-2000 (Box 554)
    - F - G, 1860-2000 (Box 555)
    - F - G, 1860-2000 (Box 556)
    - G - H, 1860-2000 (Box 557)
      Includes Gilpin.
    - G - H, 1860-2000 (Box 558)
    - G - H, 1860-2000 (Box 559)
    - G - H, 1860-2000 (Box 560)
    - H - K, 1860-2000 (Box 561)
    - H - K, 1860-2000 (Box 562)
    - H - K, 1860-2000 (Box 563)
    - K - L, 1860-2000 (Box 564)
    - K - L, 1860-2000 (Box 565)
    - K - L, 1860-2000 (Box 566)
    - K - L, 1860-2000 (Box 567)
    - L - N, 1860-2000 (Box 568)
    - L - N, 1860-2000 (Box 569)
    - L - N, 1860-2000 (Box 570)
    - L - N, 1860-2000 (Box 571)
    - M, 1860-2000 (Box 572)
    - M, 1860-2000 (Box 573)
    - M, 1860-2000 (Box 574)
    - M, 1860-2000 (Box 575)
    - P - S, 1860-2000 (Box 576)
    - P - S, 1860-2000 (Box 577)
    - P - S, 1860-2000 (Box 578)
    - S, 1860-2000 (Box 579)
      Includes W. E. Smith
    - S, 1860-2000 (Box 580)
    - S, 1860-2000 (Box 581)
    - S, 1860-2000 (Box 582)
    - S, 1860-2000 (Box 583)
    - W. E. Smith, 1860-2000 (Box 584)
    - W. E. Smith, 1860-2000 (Box 585)
    - W. E. Smith, 1860-2000 (Box 586)
    - W. E. Smith, 1860-2000 (Box 587)
    - T - V, 1860-2000 (Box 588)
    - T - V, 1860-2000 (Box 589)
    - T - V, 1860-2000 (Box 590)
    - W, 1860-2000 (Box 591)
    - W, 1860-2000 (Box 592)
    - W, 1860-2000 (Box 593)
    - W, 1860-2000 (Box 594)
    - Press prints, transparencies, slides: A - C, undated (Box 595)
      Includes Van Cleve.
    - Press prints, transparencies, slides: D - NO, undated (Box 596)
    - Press prints, transparencies, slides: M - Z, undated (Box 597)
      Includes Gilpin, O'Sullivan, W. Eugene Smith, Michael Kenna, Edward Curtis, Burkett, Forster.
    - Slides and negatives, undated (Box 598)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 599)
    - W. Eugene Smith, undated (Box 600)
    - W. Eugene Smith, undated (Box 601)
    - W. Eugene Smith, undated (Box 602)
    - W. Eugene Smith, undated (Box 603)
    - Master set binders, 1990-1993 (Box 604)
      Includes W. Eugene Smith and Robert Frank.
    - Hayden volumes, undated (Box 605)
    - Hayden volumes, undated (Box 606)
    - Dennis Lessard, circa 2007 (Box 607)
    - Dennis Lessard, undated (Box 608)
    - Dennis Lessard, undated (Box 609)
    - Dennis Lessard, undated (Box 610)
    - Photographic proof with negatives, circa 1980 (Box 611)
    - Photograph portfolio and gallery mock ups., circa 1990 (Box 612)
  - Andrew Smith personal papers, Series VII
    - Personal papers, 1990-2007 (Box 613)
    - Personal financial papers, 1990-2007 (Box 614)
    - Andrew Smith personal papers, 1970-1989 (Box 615)
    - Personal papers, 1970-1989 (Box 616)
    - Personal papers, 1970-1989 (Box 617)
    - Personal papers, 1963-1983 (Box 618)
    - Personal papers, 1963-1983 (Box 619)
    - Personal papers, 1963-1983 (Box 620)
    - Personal papers, undated (Box 621)
    - Personal papers, undated (Box 622)
    - Personal papers, undated (Box 623)
    - Personal papers, undated (Box 624)
    - Personal financial records
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until January 1, 2040. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
      - Personal financial records, 1990-2006 (Box 625)
      - Personal financial records, 1990-2006 (Box 626)
      - Personal financial records, 1970-1989 (Box 627)
      - Personal financial records, 1990-1999 (Box 628)
      - Personal financial records, 1990-1999 (Box 629)
      - Personal financial records, 1990-1999 (Box 630)
      - Personal financial records, 1991-2004 (Box 631)
      - Personal financial records, 1991-2004 (Box 632)
      - Personal financial records, 1990s-2000s (Box 633)
      - Personal financial records, 1990s-2000s (Box 634)
      - Personal financial records, 1980-1999 (Box 635)
      - Personal financial records, 1980-1999 (Box 636)
      - Personal financial records, 1980-1999 (Box 637)
      - Personal financial records, 1993-2006 (Box 638)
      - Personal financial records, 1993-2006 (Box 639)
      - Personal financial records, 1993-2006 (Box 640)
  - Audiovisual material, Series VIII
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Videocassettes, (34 videocassettes)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile.
      - The Color of Three: The Making of a Dye Transfer Print by John Wawrzonek, 1986; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398579)
      - Colores! "New Mexico's Nuclear Enchantment", 1991; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398587)
      - Colores! "Anne Noggle", 1991; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398595)
        Running time: 25:44
      - c.a.b., creative agency baden ag, Switzerland, undated; 1; NTSC (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398611)
      - Kind Nature's Scenery to Portray: The Life and Work of William E. Hook, undated; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398603)
      - "Edward S. Curtis Portfolios", undated; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398637)
        The contents of this videocassette are listed below.
        The North American Indian
        Apache, Jicarillas, Navaho
        Pima, Papago, Mohave
        Sioux, Assiniboin
        Apsaroke, Hidatsa
        Mandan, Arikara, Atsina
        Piegan, Cheyenne, Atrapaho
        Yakima, Kalispel, Flathead
        Nez Perce, Umatilla, Cayuse
        Salishan Tribes - Puget Sound
        Kawakiutl
        Nootka, Haida
        Hopi, Walpi
        Hupa, Yurok, Klamath
        Pomo, Maidu, Miwok
        Shoshoneans, Dieguenos, Washo
        Taos, Acoma, Santo Domingo
        Tewa, Zuni, Santa Clara
        Chipewyan, Cree, Blackfoot
        Wichita, So. Cheyenne, Oto
        Nunivak, Alaskan
      - Colores! "Betty Hahn", 1991; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398629)
      - "Lucien Aigner: A Life with the Camera", 1987; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398645)
        Running time: 28:33
      - Colores! "Eliot Porter", 1991; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398652)
      - Photoprofiles "Barbara Morgan", 1983; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398678)
        Running time: 28:56
      - Photoprofiles "Willard Van Dyke", 1983; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398686)
        Running time: 30:26
      - Photoprofiles "Aaron Siskind", 1985; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398694)
      - "The Photographer", Willard Van Dyke, 1948; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398702)
        Running time: 27 minutes, black and white
      - Laura Gilpin: An Enduring Grace, 1986; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398710)
        Running time: 28 minutes.
      - Capturing Grace: Barbara Van Cleve, 1993; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398728)
      - Photoprofiles "Eliot Porter", 1983; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398736)
        Running time: 30:30
      - Unknown, undated; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398744)
        This tape is security camera footage of what appears to be a gallery.
      - Antarctica, Jody and Pete Forster, 1995; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398751)
      - Photoprofiles "Ralph Steiner", 1983; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398769)
        Running time: 30:10.
      - "American Images - FSA Photogs, 1935-1942", Amarillo, TX, 1979; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398777)
        Running time: 60 minutes
      - W. Eugene Smith, master, 1989; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398785)
      - Paul Caponigro, TV spot, undated; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398793)
        Paul Caponigro is an American photographer.
      - Rooted in the Earth: The Photography of Barbara Van Cleve", 2000; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398801)
      - Photoprofiles "Betty Hahn", 1983; 1 (Box 641, Item barcode 39002091398660)
      - Montana Photographer, Barbara Van Cleve, 1999 May 19; 1 (Box 642, Item barcode 39002091396037)
      - Annie Leibovitz interview, "Person of the Week", 1991 July 12; 1 (Box 642, Item barcode 39002091396045)
        The Annie Leibovitz segment on ABC's World News Tonight runs from 10:55-15:20.
      - A World of Opportunity Sothebys.com Associates, undated; 1 (Box 642)
        This is a commercial tape. It has not been digitized.
      - Victor Masayesva, undated; 1 (Box 642, Item barcode 39002091396052)
      - unknown, undated; 1 (Box 642, Item barcode 39002091396060)
        The man on tape identifies himself as Tom Weatherall. He displays a number of prints for the video camera.
      - unknown, 1992 December 26; 1 (Box 642, Item barcode 39002091396078)
        The video appears to show the inside of an art gallery.
      - Arizona PBS, Nagatani Excavations at CCP, 2001; 1 (Box 644, Item barcode 39002091396011)
      - Lonesome Dove, 1988; 1 (Box 644)
      - Antiques Roadshow, 1997; 1 (Box 644)
        This is a commerical tape. It has not been digitized.
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 644, Item barcode 39002091396029)
    - Audiocassettes, (30 audiocassettes, 2 empty cases)
      - Thursday, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395690)
      - Friday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395708)
      - Monday no. 2, office, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395716)
      - Sunday, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395724)
      - Friday no. 3, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395732)
      - Wednesday, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395740)
      - Monday, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395757)
      - Friday no. 3, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395765)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395773)
      - Friday no. 2, office, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395781)
      - Sunday no. 2, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395799)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395807)
      - Friday no. 4, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395815)
      - Friday no. 1, office, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395823)
      - Saturday, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395880)
      - Tuesday, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395831)
      - Sunday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395898)
      - Monday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395906)
      - Tuesday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395914)
      - Wednesday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395872)
      - Thursday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395922)
      - Friday no. 1, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395856)
      - Friday no. 2, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395849)
      - Friday no. 4, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395864)
      - Archive: made on 2/4/93, 1991 December 31; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395930)
      - Archive 2: made on 2/4/93, 1991 December 31; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395948)
      - Archive 3, 1991 December 31; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395955)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 643, Item barcode 39002091395963)
      - blank tape (Box 643)
      - Untitled (audiocassette), undated; 1 (Box 645, Item barcode 39002091394917)
    - Mad Dogs & Okies (compact disc) (Box 645)
  - Electronic media, Series IX
    Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Electronic media, 2000-2010
      - JACK SPENCER, 2014-wa-16-0824; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Disk #09, 2014-wa-16-0825; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Back up 3/7/06, 2014-wa-16-0826; 1 (Box 654)
      - Database Images 12/10/03, 2014-wa-16-0827; 1 (Box 654)
      - Data Backup DVD #11, 2014-wa-16-0828; 1 (Box 654)
      - Back up DVD #10 5/16/05, 2014-wa-16-0829; 1 (Box 654)
      - Back up Artists SL-Z, 2014-wa-16-0830; 1 (Box 654)
      - Backup Artists L-R, 2014-wa-16-0831; 1 (Box 654)
      - Database Images 01/27/03, 2014-wa-16-0832; 1 (Box 654)
      - 7-1, 2014-wa-16-0833; 1 (Box 654)
      - [no label information], 2014-wa-16-0834; 1 (Box 654)